guildlaunch.com 2019-11-21

# Privacy Policy | GamerLaunch Guild, Clan & Team Hosting

## In Short

  * Gamer Launch **does not** sell or share your personally identifying info under any conditions.
  * Gamer Launch **does not** share your personally identifying info without your consent.
  * Your info may be used to contact you regarding billing, service or account info.
  * Certain features of the site, such as forum post subscriptions, will use your email to contact you, but only at your request.
  * Your email will not be shared with your guild members by default.
  * A valid email is required to confirm your account via email

## Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy states the terms under which information about you is collected and used when accessing the Launch Media Network (“Gamer Launch”) Website.  By accessing the Website you agree to the terms set forth in this Privacy Policy.  This Privacy Policy may be modified at any time without notice by posting the modified Privacy Policy here.  You should check this Privacy Policy each time you visit the Website to identify and understand any changes made since your previous visit.  By continuing to access or use the Website, you agree to be bound by any modifications to this Privacy Policy.  Please consult the Gamer Launch Terms and Conditions for additional terms and conditions that apply to your use of and access to the Website.

_Information You Submit_  
Gamer Launch does not collect Personally Identifying Information about you, which includes, but is not limited to, your name, address, telephone number and email address, unless you voluntarily submit that information to us through our online member or subscription registration forms, by email, or any other means.

_Information We Gather Electronically_  
When you visit the Gamer Launch Website, we may automatically collect certain non-identifying information about you, such as your movement about the Website, the pages on the Website you visit most frequently, the type of browser or computer operating system you use, or the domain name of the website from which you linked to us (“Non-identifying Information”).  In addition, we may store small files on your computer’s hard drive, such as a “cookie” or similar type of file to track and target your interests.  We use this Non-identifying Information internally to help us enhance the efficiency and usefulness of the Website, for advertising purposes, and to improve customer service.  If you object to this practice, please consult your browser’s documentation for instructions on erasing or blocking cookies.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.

_Use of Information_  
Gamer Launch treats the information in our database, and any Personally Identifying Information you submit through this Website as confidential.  Any Personally Identifying or Non-identifying Information (hereinafter collectively referred to as “Information”) we gather, whether voluntarily provided by you or automatically collected, may be used for our internal business and marketing purposes.  We may use the Information to send you newsletters or information relative to the services accessible through the Website.  We do not sell or otherwise disclose such Information to third parties except as necessary to achieve the purpose for which the Information was submitted or collected, to comply with the law, law enforcement agencies, or legal process served on Gamer Launch, or if we believe, in good faith, that such disclosure is necessary to defend our rights, property, or to respond to an emergency situation.

_Links to Third Party Websites_  
This Website may contain links to other Websites owned and operated by third parties.  Please note that these websites’ privacy policies may differ from that of Gamer Launch.  Gamer Launch is not responsible for the privacy practices of those third parties and does not control the use of information provided through such third party websites.  We encourage you to read the privacy policy of any website you may visit.

_Security_  
Gamer Launch has reasonable security measures in place to protect the Personally Identifying Information you submit to us, once it is received, but we cannot be responsible for the security of information in transit.  We have taken careful measures to prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of your Personally Identifying Information.  Once we receive your Personally Identifying Information that was entered into our Website, it is stored behind a firewall.  Your Personally Identifying Information is only accessible to employees, officers, or agents of Gamer Launch who need it in order to perform their jobs.  When you communicate with Gamer Launch by e-mail, however, your communication is not necessarily secure from interception and is subject to all of the risks of electronic communication.  Gamer Launch does not guarantee the security or confidentiality of transmissions.  Gamer Launch reserves the right to update or otherwise alter our security practices if an when it deems appropriate.

_Contact Information_  
If you are concerned about the Personally Identifying Information you have provided to us, or would like to review, update or delete such Personally Identifying Information, please contact Gamer Launch at [support@gamerlaunch.com](mailto:support@gamerlaunch.com).  We will make reasonable efforts to comply with your request.

If you do not wish to receive marketing or promotional materials from Gamer Launch, please send an email to [support@gamerlaunch.com](mailto:support@gamerlaunch.com) with the words “Remove from Marketing Lists” in the subject line and re-type the email address to be removed in the text of the e-mail for verification purposes.

## General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)

All EU citizens have additional rights under the GDPR. We take GDPR seriously and will process any GDPR requests without undue delay. Email all GDPR related requests to privacy@gamerlaunch.com. Include necessary information to identify the requested action and data subject as defined by [the GDPR](https://gdpr-info.eu/).

Certain data is required to use our service. We track IP addresses for fraud and abuse prevention. Username, Handle and Email are required for account creation. Under the GDPR our legal basis for this collection is legitimate interest due to requiring of processing this data to provide our services for login, user accounts, etc.

### You can contact us at any time to:

  * Request information that Guild Launch, LLC has about you.
  * Correct any information that Guild Launch, LLC.
  * Delete information that Guild Launch, LLC has about you.

### You have the following rights under the GDPR:

  * Right to be informed
  * Right of access
  * Right of rectification
  * Right to erasure
  * Right to restrict data processing
  * Right to data portability
  * Right to object
  * Rights of automated decision-making and profiling

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Website, or your dealings with Gamer Launch, please feel free to contact Gamer Launch at the following address:

80 Johnson Ferry Rd NE,  
Atlanta, GA 30328

Or feel free to contact Gamer Launch at the following e-mail address: [support@gamerlaunch.com](mailto:support@gamerlaunch.com).

_Children's Privacy Policy_

Because some of the games we support have players under the age of 13, Gamer Launch has taken additional steps to help keep younger members safe online. While we have taken appropriate steps to encourage children to use Gamer Launch carefully and responsibly, we also encourage parents and legal guardians to spend time online with their children so that they understand the services and sites their children are participating in online. Please remind children to never give out their personal information online without permission.

In compliance with Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ('COPPA'), we have adopted the following policies regarding children under the age of 13 ('Children'):

Type and Use of Information Collected from Children 

To create a Free Account, Gamer Launch requires an e-mail address as well as a parent or legal guardian's email address for verification. 

To upgrade a member's account, Gamer Launch requires parent's correct billing information. As stated in our Terms of Service, no user under the age of 18 is permitted to complete transactions on our platform that require a purchase via credit card or other payment method.

For Free Accounts, we use your Parent or Legal Guardian e-mail address for the following purposes: 

To send a confirmation notice to the parent of their child's account registration and to request your verification that they have your consent to use an account on Gamer Launch.

To prompt you to create a Gamer Launch account that is the registered Parent or Legal Guardian account for your child's account, granting access to review activity, revoke and permit access to Gamer Launch for your dependent account(s).

We reserve the right to disclose your child's personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web Sites. 

Gamer Launch may periodically use newsletters to notify our users of all the upcoming changes, upgrades, service downtime etc. We may also alert members to special offers though Launch Media Network partners. 

Notification and Verifiable Parental Consent 

At this time, whenever Gamer Launch is aware that a user is under the age of 13, Gamer Launch requires the child submit the parent's email address. We will then provide proper parental notice of the child's use of the site, including access to review their account. When purchasing account upgrades, the receipt of payment is considered actual, verifiable consent from the parents to the child's use of our website and to any information that was divulged as reasonably necessary to process payments, verify and maintain the account.
